<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Plantique</string>
    <string name="strOrdConf">"Placed order successfully "</string>
    <string name="strOrdThank">Your order are processing. Thank you for your order</string>
    <string name="menu_drawer_open">Drawer Open</string>
    <string name="menu_drawer_close">Drawer Close</string>
    <string name="strTotal">Total</string>
    <string name="strConfirmPayment">Confirm Payment</string>
    <string name="strBackButton">Back</string>
    <string name="strtextStatus">Order Status</string>
    <string name="strOrderDetailsInfo">Order Information</string>
    <string name="strShippingAddress">Shipping Address</string>
    <string name="strPhone">PHONE</string>
    <string name="strSubTotal">Sub Total</string>
    <string name="strShipFee">Shipping Fee</string>
    <string name="strPaymentMethod">Payment Method</string>
    <string name="strDiscount">Discount</string>
    <string name="strCancel">Cancel Order</string>
    <string name="strOrdID">Order ID</string>
    <string name="strUserId">User ID</string>
    <string name="strOrder">Order</string>
    <string name="strNote">Note</string>
    <string name="strDeliveryInfo">Delivery Information</string>
    <string name="strFullName">Full Name</string>
    <string name="strCIty">City/Province\n</string>
    <string name="strWard">Ward</string>
    <string name="strDistrict">District</string>
    <string name="strAddress">"Address (House number, Street,...) "</string>
    <string name="strCOD">Cash on delivery (COD)</string>
    <string name="strTransfer">Bank Account Transfer</string>
    <string name="strConfirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="strConfirmOrd">Confirm Order</string>
    <string name="strApply">Apply</string>
    <string name="strPlaceOrder">Place Order</string>
    <string name="channel_name">Order Notifications</string>
    <string name="channel_description">Notifications for new orders</string>
    <string name="channel_id">order_channel</string>
    <string name="strBankAccNum">Account Number: 0366370098</string>
    <string name="strBank">Bank: MB Bank</string>
    <string name="strAccOwner">Account Owner: Le Chau Anh</string>
    <string name="strDeliveryPolicy">Delivery Policy</string>
    <string name="strExchangePolicy">Exchange and Return Policy</string>
    <string name="strOrderInstruction">Order Instructrion</string>
    <string name="strPrivacyPolicy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="strInspectionPolicy">Inspection Policy</string>




    <string name="policy_details">
    <![CDATA[
    <b>Policy</b><br><br>
    <b>1. Goods Inspection Policy</b><br>
    <b>Definition</b><br>
    Goods inspection is the process of checking and controlling the quantity, quality, and condition of goods during transportation, storage, or delivery. This process ensures that the goods are of the correct quantity, undamaged, and meet quality standards.<br><br>
    <b>Regulations</b><br>
    – Inspection time: Plantique accepts customers to inspect with delivery personnel at the time of receiving the goods.<br>
    – Scope of goods inspection: Customers can inspect the actual products based on confirmed criteria.<br>
    – Handling steps for non-compliance with orders: Contact the hotline or email to reach the customer care department.<br>
    – Complaint channels for customers: Complaint hotline, Email.<br>
    Hotline: 0366370098<br>
    Email: plantiqueshop01@gmail.com<br><br>
    <b>Guide to Payment Methods:</b><br>
    - Cash on Delivery (COD): Payment will be made directly to the delivery person upon receipt of the order.<br>
    - Bank Transfer: Please transfer the total amount to the designated bank account. Your order will be processed upon confirmation of payment.<br><br>
    <b>3. Shipping Information:</b><br>
    - Delivery time: Typically, orders are processed and delivered within 5 business days.<br>
    - Shipping fee: Shipping costs may vary depending on the delivery location and order weight. Please refer to the shipping policy for detailed information.<br><br>
    <b>4. Return and Refund Policy:</b><br>
    - Returns: We accept returns within 7 days of purchase. Items must be in their original condition and packaging.<br>
    - Refunds: Refunds will be processed within 7 days after the returned items are received and inspected.<br>
    - Exchange: We offer exchanges for items of equal or lesser value. Please contact our customer service for assistance.<br><br>
    <b>5. Customer Support:</b><br>
    - For any inquiries or assistance, please contact our customer service team:<br>
    + Hotline: 0938152400<br>
    + Email: plantiqueshop01@gmail.com<br><br>
    ]]>
</string>

    <string name="terms_and_conditions">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Terms and Conditions</b><br><br>

        <b>1. Introduction</b><br>
        Welcome to Plantique. By accessing our app, you agree to these terms and conditions.<br><br>

        <b>2. Privacy Policy</b><br>
        Our Privacy Policy details how we collect, use, and protect your data. For more information, please visit our Privacy Policy section on our app or website.<br><br>

        <b>3. User Responsibilities</b><br>
        You must use the app legally and refrain from prohibited activities. You must be 18 years old or have parental permission to use this app.<br><br>

        <b>4. Intellectual Property Rights</b><br>
        All content provided on the app is either owned by us or used with permission. No content may be copied, distributed, or used without prior permission.<br><br>

        <b>5. Purchases</b><br>
        If applicable, specific terms related to the purchase of goods or services will be detailed during the purchase process.<br><br>

        <b>6. User Accounts</b><br>
        If you create an account, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your device.<br><br>

        <b>7. Termination</b><br>
        We may terminate or suspend access to our app immediately, without prior notice or liability, for any reason whatsoever, including, without limitation, if you breach the Terms.<br><br>

        <b>8. Governing Law</b><br>
        These Terms will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Country/State in which our company is registered, without regard to its conflict of law provisions.<br><br>

        <b>9. Changes to Terms</b><br>
        We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Terms on our site.<br><br>

        <b>10. Contact Information</b><br>
        If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us at [contact information].
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string-array name="order_statuses">
        <item>All Statuses</item>
        <item>Processing</item>
        <item>Delivering</item>
        <item>Finished</item>
        <item>Cancelled</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="update_order_statuses">
        <item>Processing</item>
        <item>Delivering</item>
        <item>Finished</item>
        <item>Cancelled</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>